Finding Aid for the Paul D. Boyer Papers, 1943-2009 LSC.2156
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 4: Government Funding and Contracts, 1955-1995
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1991., 1990-1991 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1992-1993. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Grants: DOE, "Energy Capture and Use in Plants and Animals", Renewal Request for 1993 and grant closeout., 1992-1994 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Grants: ERDA, Renewal Request for 1976., 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Grants: ERDA, Renewal Request for 1976-1981., 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Grants: ERDA, Revised Research Proposal Guidelines., 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Grants: ERDA, Renewal Request for 1977., 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Grants: ERDA, Renewal Request for 1978., 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Grants: NIH Support Summary, 1962-1967. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Grants: NIH USPHS Supplemental Application, 1979-1980. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Grants: NIH USPHS 5 year grant, 1980-1985., 1979-1982 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Grants: NSF Proposal and Research Reports, 1952-1956. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Grants: NSF Request for 1955-1959, "The Mechanism and Control of Certain Metabolic Enzymes"., 1955-1960 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Grants: NSF Request for 1972-1976, "Mechanisms of Selected Biocatalysis" (1 of 2)., 1971-1976 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Grants: NSF Request for 1972-1976, "Mechanisms of Selected Biocatalysis" (2 of 2)., 1971-1976 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Grants: NSF Request for 1975-1981, "Energy Transducing Mechanisms in Contraction and Active Transport" (1 of 2). (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Grants: NSF Request for 1975-1981, "Energy Transducing Mechanisms in Contraction and Active Transport" (2 of 2). (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Grants: NSF Renewal Request for 1976-1977, "Energy Transducing Mechanisms in Contraction and Active Transport". (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Grants: NSF Request for 1977-1978, "Energy Transducing Mechanisms in Contraction and Active Transport"., 1976 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Grants: NSF Request for 1978, "Energy Transducing Mechanisms in Contraction and Active Transport". (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Grants: NSF Renewal Request for 1978-1979, "Energy Transducing Mechanisms in Contraction and Active Transport". (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Grants: NSF Equipment for 1979-1980, "Biological Energy Transducing Mechanisms". (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Grants: NSF Request for 1981-1987, "Energy Transducing Mechanisms in Contraction and Active Transport"., 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Grants: NSF Renewal Request for 1983-1984, "Energy Transducing Mechanisms in Contraction and Active Transport". (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Requests & Progress Reports for 1948-1955, "The Nature and Extent of Combinations and interactions of Proteins". (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Requests & Progress Reports for 1956-1960, "The Function and Properties of Enzymes"., 1956-1961 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Grants: USPHS Request for 1956-1963, "The Function and Properties of Enzymes"., circa 1963 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Grants: USPHS Request for "Physical Biochemistry Research and Laboratory Unit"., 1958-1962 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Grants: USPHS Request for 1961-1962., 1961-1963 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Grants: USPHS Applications for 1962-1963, "Studies on Oxidative Phosphorylation" and for 1963-1964, "Intermediates in Phosphorylation". (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1963., 1962-1963 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Grants: USPHS Progress Reports for 1963-1969. (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1964-1965. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1965-1970. (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1966-1967. (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Grants: USPHS Request for 1966-1967, supporting a new PhD program with the MBI., 1965 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Grants: USPHS Correspondence, 1967. (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1967-1968. (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1968-1969, "Enzyme Phosphorylation and Related Mechanisms". (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1969-1970, "Enzymic Phosphorylations and Related Mechanisms". (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Grants: USPHS Terminal Scientific Progress Report, 1970-1975. (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Grants: USPHS Application for 1970-1977, "Studies on Enzymic Phosphorylations and Related Mechanisms". (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Grants: USPHS Request for 1971-1972, "Studies on Enzymic Phosphorylations and Related Mechanics". (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1972-1973, "Enzymic Phosphorylations and Related Mechanisms". (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1973-1974. (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1974-1975. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1975-1976. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Grants: USPHS Progress Report for 1975-1979, "Studies on Enzymic Phosphorylations and Related Mechanisms"., circa 1979 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1975-1980., circa 1975 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1976-1977. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1977-1978, "Biological Energy Transducing Mechanisms". (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1978-1979, "Biological Energy Transducing Mechanisms". (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1979-1980, "Biological Energy Transducing Mechanisms". (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Grants: USPHS Supplement Request for 1979-1980. (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1980-1981, "Biological Energy Transducing Mechanisms". (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Grants: USPHS 5 year request, 1980-1985., 1980-1984 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1981-1982, "Biological Energy Transducing Mechanisms". (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1982-1983, "Biological Energy Transducing Mechanisms". (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1983-1984. (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1984-1985, "Biological Energy Transducing Mechanisms". (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1985-1986. (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Grants: USPHS 5 year Renewal for 1985-1990, "The Mechanism of ATP Synthase and Related Enzymes"., 1984-1985 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Grants: USPHS Request for 1986-1987, "The Mechanism of ATP Synthase and Related Enzymes". (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Grants: USPHS Request for 1987-1988, "The Mechanism of ATP Synthase and Related Enzymes"., 1987-1989 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Grants: USPHS Request for 1988-1989, "The Mechanism of ATP Synthase and Related Enzymes". (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1989-1990, "The Mechanism of ATP Synthase and Related Enzymes". (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1990-1991, "The Mechanism of ATP Synthase and Related Enzymes". (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Grants: USPHS Request for 1990-1995, "The Mechanism of ATP Synthase and Related Enzymes"., 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Grants: USPHS Renewal Request for 1991-1992, "The Mechanisms of ATP Synthase and Related Enzymes". (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Grants: USPHS Final Progress Report for 1992-1995, "The Mechanism of ATP Synthase and Related Enzymes"., 1992-1996 (Box 49, Folder 6)